RG 062:018, Town of Brookfield
Connecticut State Library
Town of Brookfield records
1843-1947
Connecticut State Library
Brookfield (Conn.)
22.75 cubic feet
Tax records for the town of Brookfield.
RG062_018
Multiple
Historical Note
The town of Brookfield was incorporated in May 1788 and was taken from Danbury, New Milford and Newtown.
Scope and Content
Tax records for the town of Brookfield.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Brookfield -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Brookfield -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Brookfield -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Brookfield -- Registers
Places:
Brookfield (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1843-1947
  - T000618
    - Tax abstracts
      - 1843-1844, 1845-1846, 1847-1848, 1850-1851 (Box Box 1)
      - 1852-1854, 1855-1856, 1857-1862 (Box Box 2)
      - 1863-1868, 1869-1875 (Box Box 3)
      - 1882-1885, 1886, 1887, 1888, 1890 (Box Box 4)
      - 1891, 1892, 1893, 1894, 1895, 1896 (Box Box 5)
      - 1897, 1898, 1899, 1900 (Box Box 6)
      - 1901, 1902, 1903-1904, 1905 (Box Box 7)
  - 2005-019
    - Indivudual Tax Lists
      - 1917-1944 (Box Box 1)
        On oversize shelving.
      - 1914-1925 (Box Box 2)
      - 1915, 1939-1940 (Box Box 3)
      - 1918, 1919, 1926, 1941, 1942 (Box Box 4)
      - 1920, 1929, 1933, 1944 (Box Box 5)
      - 1921, 1926, 1935, 1940 (Box Box 6)
      - 1923, 1935, 1942-1943 (Box Box 7)
      - 1931, 1945-1947 (Box Box 8)
      - 1935, 1937, 1947 (Box Box 9)